[female]庄贤惠:
你胡说八道什么呀我可什么事都没让你干
What nonsense are you talking about? I didn't ask you to do anything.
[female]庄贤惠:
别赖在我头上
Don't pin this on me.
[male]男员工:
都是你毁了我
You ruined me.
[male]男员工:
都是你一都是你
It was all you! All you!
[female]庄贤惠:
你要干什么别过来
What are you doing? Stay away!
[male]男员工:
你不仁就别怪我不义
If you're unfair, don't blame me for being ruthless.
[female]庄贤惠:
滚开滚开
Get off me! Get off me!
[male]黑衣男子:
把他给我拉开
Pull him away from her.
[male]董事长:
我的办公室不是让你们撒泼的
My office is not a place for you to make a scene.
[male]男员工:
董事长求求你再给我一次机会
Chairman, I'm begging you, give me another chance.
[male]男员工:
我还有几百万的房贷没有还
I still have a mortgage of millions to pay off.
[male]男员工:
我不能失去这份工作
I can't lose this job.
[male]董事长:
你不能失去这份工作
You can't lose this job?
[male]董事长:
要不是我夫人多才多艺
If it weren't for my multi-talented wife
[male]董事长:
霍氏这些重要合作商都被你们得罪光了
You've offended all of Huo's key business partners!
[male]董事长:
到时候就会有成百上千的员工
Then, hundreds, even thousands of employees
[male]董事长:
因为你失去工作而流离失所
will lose their jobs and homes because of you.
[male]董事长:
他们跟谁哭去
Who are they supposed to cry to?
[male]董事长:
跟错了主子做错事就要接受惩罚
You chose the wrong master. You did the wrong thing. Now, face the punishment.
[male]董事长:
收拾你的东西
Pack your things.
[male]董事长:
睡天桥去吧
Go sleep under a bridge.
[male]董事长:
我不想再看见你
I don't want to see you again.
[male]董事长:
带走
Take him away.
[male]男员工:
董事长我错了都是庄贤惠逼我干的
Chairman, I was wrong! Zhuang Xianhui made me do it!
[female]庄贤惠:
震东
Zhendong
[female]庄贤惠:
震东我真的不是故意的
Zhendong, I really didn't mean to.
[female]庄贤惠:
我知道错了
I know I was wrong.